所以安静，小宝贝，不要哭，你知道你的爸爸一定会死。
So hush, little baby don't you cry you know your daddy's bound to die.
但我所有的考验，主啊很快就会结束
But all my trials, lord soon be over
乔。
Jo.
——荣耀。荣耀,荣耀。
- Glory. - Glory, glory.
哈利路亚，他的真理正在行进
Hallelujah his truth is marching
他的真理在前进
His truth is marching
约翰,妈妈的家里。
John, mom's home.
好吧。
Okay.
好吧。嗯。
Okay. Mmm.
服务员!
Waiter!
我们需要一些音乐。
We need some music.
像个傻瓜。
Like a fool.
对我刻薄残忍，干杯。
Treat me mean and cruel, cheers.
但是爱我。
But love me.
绞紧我忠实的心。
Wring my faithful heart.
-把它撕成碎片-嘿，妈妈
- Tear it all apart, - hey, mom?
-但是爱我吧-妈妈!
- But love me - mom!
你想把音乐关小点吗?我们明天还要上学。
You want to turn down the music? We've got school tomorrow.
约翰尼,pammie,嗨。这是史蒂夫。
Johnny, pammie, hi. This is Steve.
周二晚上我们遇到了史蒂夫。
We met Steve on Tuesday night.
——嗨,孩子。——你做了吗?
- Hi, kids. - You did?
——周五还。——星期六。
- Friday also. - Saturday too.
-我会伤心难过的。-哦，对不起。
- I'll be sad and blue. - Oh, I'm sorry.
-为你哭泣。-请把声音关小一点。
- Cryin' over you. - Just turn it down a little, please.
——好的。晚安，孩子们。
- Okay. - Good night, kids.
哦,男孩。
Oh, boy.
-我们去睡觉吧。-会乞讨和偷窃。
- Let's go to sleep. - Would beg and steal.
-乞讨和偷窃。-只是去感受。
- Beg and steal. - Just to feel.
什么?
What?
我不想再跳舞了。
I don't feel like dancing anymore.
-那我们上楼吧——不,不。
- Well, let's go upstairs. - No, no.
好吧,什么?
Well, what?
它是不正确的。
It's not right.
我觉得你该回家了。
I think you should go home.
-你真的想让我去吗?-我要你走。它是不正确的。
- You really want me to go? - I want you to go. It's not right.
——好!-哦，好孤独
- Fine! - Oh, so lonely
因为我觉得我的灵魂在燃烧推动着我带我走得更高我看到我的灵魂在燃烧。
'Cause I feel my soul on fire pushin' me on takin' me higher I see my soul on fire.
谁能抗拒这样的感觉。
Who can resist a feeling like this.
灵魂着火了。
Soul on fire.
哇!伙计，我们今天准备好了，不是吗?
Whoa! Man, we're ready for today, aren't we?
你在开玩笑吧。你知道他们又要裁我们了。
You gotta be kiddin'. You know they're gonna cut us again.
你了吗?我们比以前踢得更好了。我们踢。
Are you whacked? We play better than ever. We kick.
他们会凭空找个狗屁借口。
They're gonna pull some kind of bullshit excuse right out of left field.
-去年是什么?——着装。我们不合群。
- What was it last year? - Dress code. We didn't fit in.
好吧，那我们就自保吧。
All right, so we cover our asses.
-我们要让这些人找不到任何借口。-是的。
- We make it so these guys can't come up with any excuses. - Yeah.
你哥哥还在泰勒燕尾服公司工作吗?
Your brother still work at Taylor tux?
是的。为什么?哦,不,约翰。不可能。
Yeah. Why? Oh, no, John. No way.
猴子西装。不可能。
Monkey suits. No way.
——没有。他是对的。-拜托，伙计们。
- No way. He's right. - Come on, you guys.
这个才艺表演是我们唯一能玩的地方。
This talent show is the only place we could play, man.
我们已经连续三年被裁了。你知道会有多少人去吗?
Three years in a row we've been cut. You know how many people are gonna be there?
约翰!早餐!
John! Breakfast!
我要走了。以后再见。
I gotta go. See ya later.
-普通38码，伙计。——38普通。
- Thirty-eight regular, man. - Thirty-eight regular.
糖味在哪里?
Where are the sugar smacks?
你最近营养不足。
You're not getting enough nutrition lately.
吃那些糖衣垃圾会堵塞你的血液。
Eating that sugarcoated crap clogs your blood.
我们没糖了?
We out of sugar smacks?
-你们俩是怎么回事?-你有负罪感吗?
- What is it with you two? - You feeling guilty about something?
-你说什么?-你听到了。
- What did you say? - You heard me.
为什么每次我想做点好事…你要把它扭曲成自私和卑鄙的东西吗?
Why is it every time I try to do something nice... You've got to twist it into something selfish and mean?
我看到什么就说什么。
I call 'em like I see 'em.
-我不喜欢你看他们的方式-我也是，妈
- I don't like the way you see 'em. - Me neither, ma.
我讨厌你评论我的私生活。这是我的事。
I'm sick of you commenting on my private life. It is my business.
一旦你的私生活开始干扰我和帕米的生活…那它也变成我的事了。
As soon as your private life starts interfering with my life and pammie's life... Then it becomes my business too.
一天又一天，我越来越困惑。
Day after day I'm more confused.
然而我在倾盆大雨中寻找光明。
Yet I look for the light through the pouring rain.
你知道这是一场我讨厌输的比赛，我感到压力很大。
You know that's a game that I hate to lose, and I'm feelin' the strain.
真可惜。
Ain't it a shame.
哦，给我节奏，男孩们，解放我的灵魂。
Oh, give me the beat, boys and free my soul.
和渐渐疏远……
And drift away...
-她很好，不是吗?-哦,是的。
- She's good, isn't she? - Oh, yes.
这太酷了，伙计。
This is so cool, man.
她在演鲍勃·迪伦，那些蠢货还不知道呢。
She's playing Bob Dylan, and those bozos don't even know it.
我们赢越南战争的机会比和那样的女孩在一起要大得多。
We got a better chance of winning the Vietnam war than making it with a girl like that.
闭嘴。
Shut up.
优秀的,贝丝。
Excellent, Beth.
-是德彪西吗?——没有。一位不知名的美国作曲家。
- Was that debussy? - No. An obscure American composer.
哦,是的。好,祝贺你。
Oh, yes. Well, congratulations.
周六下午彩排时见。
We'll see you at rehearsal Saturday afternoon.
好的,谢谢你。
Okay, thank you.
约翰尼·沃尔夫……和wolfepack。
Johnny wolfe... And the wolfepack.
嗨。这是我写的一首歌。叫做"灵魂燃烧"
Hi. This is a song I wrote. It's called “soul on fire.”
灵魂在燃烧灵魂在燃烧。
Soul on fire soul on fire now.
哈!
Huh!
有件事让我很伤心我说的是那场血腥的战争。
There's somethin' that's hurtin' me I'm talkin' about that bloody war.
一个国家的孩子正在死去。
Where children are dyin' in a country.
那不能再多了。
That can't take much more.
这是一场生存之战。
It's a fight for survival.
如果我独自战斗
And if I fight all alone
我要打败所有的对手。
I'm gonna beat every rival.
停止它!我说，住手!
Stop it! Stop it, I say!
不会放手，因为我感觉我的灵魂在燃烧
Won't let go 'cause I feel my soul on fire...
非常感谢，沃尔夫先生。
Thank you very much, Mr. Wolfe.
就是这样,男人吗?你不让我们把话说完?
That's it, man? You're not gonna let us finish?
抱歉，但我们觉得歌词不太好。
I'm sorry, but we find the lyrics objectionable.
对象……啊,来吧。
Object... ah, come on.
去年你说这是着装要求。
Last year you said it was the dress code.
一年前，你说她们的头发太长了。
A year before that, you said their hair was too long.
前年，你说我们要在合唱团上一学期的课才有资格。
The year before that, you said we had to take a semester of that glee club to qualify.
你其实是说你不喜欢摇滚。
What you're really saying is that you don't like rock 'n' roll.
那不是真的。去年，米奇·恩格尔唱了一首摇滚歌曲。
That's not true. Last year, Mitch engle sang a rock song.
他在木匠旁边唱《靠近你》。那不是摇滚。
He sang “close to you” by the carpenters. That's not rock 'n' roll.
——沃尔夫先生!——我很抱歉。
- Mr. Wolfe! - I'm sorry.
我们为此付出了很多努力。
We worked really hard for this.
这些礼服都是租来的。只要你能给我们一次机会。
We rented these tuxes and all. If you would just give us a chance.
——我很抱歉。-约翰，没事的。
- I'm sorry. - John, that's all right, man.
求你了，先生，给我一个机会。
Please, sir, just a chance.
请离开舞台。我们还得继续试镜。
Please get off the stage. We have to continue with the auditions.
没事的，伙计。没关系。
It's all right, man. It's all right.
别担心。
Don't worry about it.
——为什么?——谢谢。
- Why? - Thank you.
邦妮·罗文三人组。
The Bonnie Rowan trio.
你不讨厌每天晚上打扫这个地方吗?
Don't you hate cleaning this place up every night?
反正也没人来过这里。
I mean, no one ever comes here anyway.
妈妈觉得有一天会有人来做客。
Mom figures we might get a guest someday.
我猜这地方让她想起了爸爸。
I guess this place reminds her of dad.
我听说他有了新家庭。
I heard he's got a new family and everything.
帕米，那不是真的。
Pammie, that's not true.
爸爸不是那种想要家庭的人。
Dad's not the kind of guy who wants a family.
如果他是，他就会回来和我们在一起。
If he was, he'd be back here with us.
对吧?对吧?
Right? Right?
-嗨。妈，地板是湿的。
- Hi. - Ma, the floor's wet.
好吧。你可以把它收起来了。
Okay. You can put that away.
——走吧。-我们要去哪里?
- Let's go. - Where're we going?
-我们要去露天影院看埃尔维斯的双场演出。-帕米要学习。
- We're going to an Elvis double feature at the drive-in. - Pammie's got to study.
-她可以在后座学习。-为什么我们一定要看猫王的电影?
- She can study in the backseat. - Why do we have to see an Elvis movie?
为什么我们看不到一些很酷的东西?我们去看教父吧。
Why can't we see something cool? Let's go see the godfather.
像你这么大的孩子能从国王那里学到很多。
A boy your age can learn a lot from the king.
他不再是国王了。他很久以前就失去了。
He isn't the king anymore. He lost that a long time ago.
-他仍然是国王。-我要告诉你多少次?
- He is still the king. - How many times I gotta tell ya?
他的头发满是油脂。
His hair is full of oil and grease.
他脸上都是毛茸茸的小羊排。
He's got big ol' hairy lamb chops on his face.
他所有的歌都是关于夏威夷的。他拍的电影很烂。
All his songs are about Hawaii. He makes lousy movies.
而且他吉他弹得很烂，妈妈。皮特·汤森德会浪费他的。
And he sucks at guitar, mom. Pete townshend would waste him.
告诉我。像我这样的人能从他身上学到什么?
Tell me. What is a guy like me gonna learn from a guy like that?
曾几何时，每个男人都想成为猫王。
There was a time when every guy wanted to be Elvis.
如果你想从猫王身上学点什么……注意他对待女人的方式。
If you want to learn something from Elvis... Watch the way he treats women.
你会让学校里的每个女孩都想和你约会。
You'll have every girl at school wanting a date with you.
来吧。来吧,pammie。
Come on. Come on, pammie.
来吧。它会很有趣。
Come on. It'll be fun.
嘿,你,鬓角。下面有个小妞想听你唱歌。
Hey, you, sideburns. I got a chick down there wants to hear you sing.
-对不起，先生，我…——这是纯粹的。
- I'm sorry, sir, I... - It's pure.
纯的。
Pure.
什么?
What?
猫王。
Elvis.
他是那么纯洁，那么干净，就像……像乳白色的肥皂泡沫，上面覆盖着甜甜的奶油。
He's so pure, so clean, like... Like ivory soap suds covered with sweet cream.
这是我听你说过的最老套的话了。
That's about the corniest thing I've ever heard you say.
——嗯,抢劫。——纯粹的。
- Well, heist. - Pure.
你爸爸有点像猫王。
You know, your dad was a little like Elvis.
——没有。是他吗?——嗯。
- No. Was he? - Mm-hmm.
有一次，我们结婚八周年纪念的时候…你爸爸买了艘新划艇，爱尔兰之雾。
You know, once, for our eighth wedding anniversary... Your dad got this new rowboat, the Irish mist.
我们在月光下乘船去了凉亭。
We took it out for a moonlight sail to the gazebo.
我们喝了啤酒，吃了披萨……我们就在凉亭里做爱了。
And we had beer and pizza... And we made love right there in the gazebo.
啊,来吧。
Ah, come on.
我们确实偶尔做爱。
Well, we did occasionally make love.
这是正常的。你以为你是哪来的?
It's normal. Where in the hell do you think you came from?
我知道。但现在我每次出海，都会想起你们俩一起玩。
I know. But now every time I take a boat ride, I'm gonna think of you two goin' at it.
噢。
Oooh.
总之，在我们做爱之后…-他拿着他的吉他…-爸爸弹吉他?
Anyway, after we make love... - He gets his guitar... - Dad played guitar?
不。没有，但他自学了三个和弦……就为了给我唱我最爱的猫王之歌《爱我》
No. No, but he taught himself three chords... Just so he could sing me my favorite Elvis song, “love me.”
然后他开始唱歌，他的声音很平淡……沙哑的，就像我有时听到你唱歌一样。
And he starts singing, and his voice is real flat... And gravelly, like when I hear you singing sometimes.
——谢谢。——不!
- Thanks. - No!
但那是真的，是真的……这真的很有意义。它是真实的…
But it was, it was real... It was real meaningful. It was real...
它是如此美丽。
It was so beautiful.
我都快哭出来了。
You know, I almost started to cry.
我有……我俯身给了他一个拥抱。把吉他撞进水里。
I had... I leaned over to give him a hug... And knocked the guitar into the water.
它飘走了。
It floated away.
我们再也没有拿回来。
We never got it back.
我猜这有点毁了周年纪念，对吧?
Guess it kinda ruined the anniversary, huh?
我一直以为……你知道，如果我当时把那把吉他留下…我可能挽救了我们的婚姻。
I always thought... You know, if I'd just saved that guitar... I might've saved our marriage.
我永远不可能像猫王那样。
I could never be like Elvis.
-为什么不呢，亲爱的?-我不能留好鬓角。
- Why not, honey? - I can't grow good sideburns.
你是做什么的?-从事汽车配件工作。为什么?
- What do you do for a living? - Work in auto accessories. Why?
我唱歌是有报酬的，我觉得你应该为我做任何事。
I usually get paid for singin', and I figure you oughta do whatever you do for me.
给我的车装一套新的座套怎么样?
So how about putting a new set of seat covers on my car?
为什么,当然,鬓角。你想要什么颜色?
Why, sure, sideburns. What color you want?
我觉得他是黄色的，你说呢?
I figure his color's yellow, don't you?
你相信这个吗?这太假了。
You believe this? This is so fake.
——看它。-我看不下去了
- Watch it. - I can't watch it.
强尼，你的吉他怎么会在这里?
Johnny, what's your guitar doing here?
今天有个试镜。我们得到削减。
There was an audition today. We got cut.
哦。你想谈谈吗?
Oh. Do you want to talk about it?
是的。我去哄帕米睡觉。
Yeah. Let me just put pammie to bed.
好吧。
Okay.
-帕米，我把灯关了。——没有。
- Pammie, I'm gonna turn out this light. - No.
-就今晚。-不，拜托。
- Just for tonight. - No, come on.
你知道黑暗的作用。
You know what dark does.
- Pam。-他们出来的时候是黑暗的。黏糊糊的灵魂吸吮者。
- Pam. - Dark's when they come out. The slimy soul suckers.
-那是个童话。——不是!
- That's a fairy tale. - Is not!
露西·切斯威克的表妹被一个黏糊糊的吸血鬼抓走了。
Lucy cheswick's cousin got taken by a slimy soul sucker.
露西·切斯威克的表妹死于肺炎。
Lucy cheswick's cousin died of pneumonia.
没有。他们停电了。一个黏糊糊的吸魂者从黑暗中渗出…把它五英尺长的锋利指甲塞进露西表妹的嘴里……
Did not. Their electricity went out... And a slimy soul sucker oozed out of the darkness... Put its five-foot sharp fingernails into Lucy's cousin's mouth...
从里面挖出她的灵魂。
Reached way down inside and scooped out her soul.
你相信吗?
And you believe that?
她死了，不是吗?
Well, she's dead, isn't she?
你知道，我睡觉的时候关灯。他们怎么不懂我?
You know, I sleep with my lights off. How come they don't get me?
黏糊糊的吸血鬼只杀小女孩。
Slimy soul suckers only kill little girls.
对了，我忘了。我真笨。
That's right, I forgot. How stupid of me.
晚安，亲爱的。-晚安，约翰。
- Good night, honey. - Good night, John.
——那是什么?-我不知道。
- What's that? - I don't know.
闭上眼睛，睡觉。这两个你。
Close your eyes, go to sleep. Both of you.
玛丽!
Marie!
宝贝，我20分钟后回来。
Hey, baby I'll be back in 20 minutes.
-我们到时候再谈，好吗?——确定。无论什么。
- We can talk then, okay? - Sure. Whatever.
- 20分钟。——正确的。
- Twenty minutes. - Right.
他是个大男孩。他会照顾好自己的。
He's a big boy. He'll take care of himself.
你没关前门。
You left your front door open.
有些人失业一年了，就为了找个工作。
There's guys out there been out of work a year, just lookin' for an open front door.
他们进来，打开你的喉咙，偷走你的天顶……- 20秒后。-你来告诉我前门开着吗?
They come in, open up your throat, and steal your zenith... - In 20 seconds. - You came in here to tell me that my front door is open?
不。这是你的妈妈。
No. It's your mom.
别担心，她会没事的。
Don't worry, she's gonna be okay.
她在医院里
She's in the hospital.
这就是猫王现在的样子吗，艾琳阿姨?
Is that how Elvis looks now, aunt Irene?
——嗯。-不喜欢他穿的白色西装。
- Mm-hmm. - Don't like that white suit he's wearing.
既不做。
Neither do.
他穿得好像在日记女王之类的地方工作。
He dresses like he works at the diary queen or something.
看。上面说埃尔维斯周六会来克利夫兰。
Look. It says Elvis is coming to Cleveland on Saturday.
-约翰，我们能去看看他吗?-我不这么认为。
- John, can we go see him? - Don't think so.
-妈妈会喜欢的。-我知道她会喜欢的。
- Mom would love it. - I know she'd love it.
但我觉得她还会在这里。
But I thinks she's still gonna be here.
别担心。
Don't worry about a thing.
我来照顾孩子们，你照顾好你自己。
I'll take care of the kids, and you take care of yourself.
好吧。谢谢。
Okay. Thanks.
帕米，去跟你妈妈打个招呼。
Pammie, go say hi to your mommy.
-发生了什么事?-史蒂夫喝酒了。
- What happened? - Steve was drinking.
结果他出了车祸。
And he got into an accident.
-她会没事吧?-是的，她会没事的。
- Is she gonna be all right? - Yeah, she'll be all right.
她有轻微脑震荡和几根肋骨擦伤。
She has a slight concussion and a couple bruised ribs.
她的眼睛怎么了?
What happened to her eye?
我猜她和史蒂夫吵架了。
Hmm, I guess she and Steve had a fight.
他打她吗?
He hit her?
-他在医院吗?-不，他们放了他
- Is he here in the hospital? - No, they released him.
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
强尼，别这样，放松。好吧?
Johnny, come on, relax. Okay?
别让你妈妈不高兴。
Don't upset your mom.
她会没事的。
She's gonna be all right.
我很抱歉。你是对的。
I'm sorry. You're right.
-我去跟她谈谈-是的。
- I'm gonna go talk to her. - Yeah.
我很快就回家。
I'll be home soon.
嘿,紧急刹车。
Hey, scram.
嘿,妈妈。——嗨,约翰尼。
- Hey, mom. - Hi, Johnny.
漫长的20分钟，是吧?
Long 20 minutes, huh?
是的。
Yeah.
嘿,妈?
Hey, ma?
你觉得我们还能和好吗?
You think we'll ever be okay again?
我是说，像平常一样。
I mean, like normal.
是的。
Yeah.
确定。
Sure.
每天当我醒来…我希望情况会好转。
Every day when I wake up... I hope things'll get better.
他们从不做。
They never do.
也许你可以告诉我，妈妈。我能帮你什么忙吗?
Maybe if you could just tell me, mom. What can I do to help you?
我要怎么做才能让你再开心起来?
What can I do that's gonna make you happy again?
我不知道。
I don't know.
听着，你待在这里。好吧?不要动。
Listen, you stay right here. Okay? Don't move.
嗨,约翰。
Hi, John.
怎么了什么”?
How ya doin'?
离我妈远点。
You stay away from my mother.
你在看什么?你在看什么?
What are you looking at? What were you watching?
像对待傻瓜一样对待我。
Treat me like a fool.
对我刻薄残忍。
Treat me mean and cruel.
但是爱我。
But love me.
绞紧我忠实的心。
Wring my faithful heart.
撕裂一切，但爱我。-你不爱我吗?
Tear it all apart - but love me. - Won't you love me.
伙计们，我需要你们的帮助。
Guys, I need your help.
是吗?怎么了,伙计?
Yeah? What's up, man?
我们要让我妈和猫王约会。
We're gonna give my mom a date with Elvis Presley.
你打算怎么办?绑架他?
What are you gonna do? Kidnap him?
-不惜一切代价-拜托，伙计。
- Whatever it takes. - Come on, man.
我们要飞去孟菲斯还是好莱坞还是他住的什么鬼地方?
We gonna fly to Memphis or Hollywood or wherever the hell he lives?
不，他下周六在克利夫兰打球。
No, he's playing in Cleveland next Saturday.
这家伙有900个保镖。
The guy's got like 900 bodyguards.
-我们会带着枪进去，对吧?——机枪。
- We're gonna go in with guns, right? - Machine guns.
没有机枪，就没有暴力。会很安全的。
No machine guns, no violence. It's gonna be real safe.
如果我们因为绑架而被捕…-我们应该因为绑架被捕…-米克·贾格尔!
If we're gonna get arrested for kidnapping somebody... - We should get arrested for kidnapping... - Mick Jagger!
-米克·贾格尔!-我们不会被逮捕的
- Mick Jagger! - We're not gonna get arrested.
而且，我只要离他近一点就能跟他说话。
Besides, I just gotta get close enough to talk to him.
也许我们能说服他和我们一起回来
Maybe we could convince him to come back with us.
他和我们一样是个普通人。
He's a regular guy like us.
像我们这样的普通人没有5000万美元…他有私人飞机，每晚睡不同的女孩。
A regular guy like us doesn't have $50 million... His own private jet, and a different girl in bed every night.
我要告诉你们多少次我是认真的?
How many times do I got to tell you guys that I'm serious?
你们知道我妈妈的事。她的……她有大麻烦了，伙计。
You guys know about my mom. She's... She's in a lot of trouble, man.
她爱猫王胜过一切。
And she loves Elvis Presley more than anything.
我想，如果我能让她开心…也许我能让我们的家庭团结起来。
And I figure, you know, if I can make her happy... Then maybe I can hold our family together.
哈!看看这个。猫王香水。
Ha! Check this out. Elvis perfume.
-猫王狗牌。猫王口红。——猫王按钮。
- Elvis dog tags. Elvis lipstick. - Elvis buttons.
有什么东西是这家伙没装出来的吗?
Is there anything this guy didn't put his face on?
-我知道了。我知道怎么接近埃尔维斯了。——如何?
- I've got it. I know how we can get close to Elvis. - How?
-我们给他送了披萨。——一个披萨吗?
- We send him a pizza. - A pizza?
打扮成送披萨的，走过去敲他的门。
Dress up like a pizza delivery guy, walk up and knock on his door.
-你来了。它是美丽的。——正确的。
- And there you are. It's beautiful. - Right.
那当他说…"我没点披萨，儿子" ?
Then what do I do when he says... “I didn't order a pizza, son”?
这是你跟他谈谈的机会，说服他跟你回家。
That's your chance to talk to him, convince him to come home with ya.
这是没有好。周围会有很多人。
It's no good. There's gonna be too many people around.
我得让他远离所有人。我们得让他一个人待着。
I've gotta get him away from everyone. We have to have him alone.
罗西。
Rosie.
——罗西?——罗西?-披萨女?
- Rosie? - Rosie? - The pizza lady?
看看这个，伙计。罗西长得很像格拉迪斯·普雷斯利。
Check this out, man. Rosie looks a lot like Gladys Presley.
——猫王的母亲。——哇!
- Elvis's mother. - Wow!
-他们长得一点都不像。-你只是在看表面的东西。点击这里查看详情！
- They don't look anything alike. - You're just lookin" at the surface stuff. Check it out!
他们有一样的眼睛，一样的脸。
They've got the same eyes, same face.
她要怎么帮我们抓到埃尔维斯?
How's she supposed to help us get Elvis?
埃尔维斯非常喜欢他的母亲。他爱她胜过一切。
Elvis was crazy about his mother. He loved her more than anything.
但这里说她已经死了十多年了。
But it says here she's been dead over ten years.
没关系。
It doesn't matter.
埃尔维斯是个很有激情的人。
Elvis is like an intense kind of guy.
他相信占星术和中东超自然的鬼话。
He believes in all that astrological and middle eastern supernatural bullshit.
我明白了。我们要扰乱他的头脑。
I get it. We're gonna mess with his head.
——恭喜你,罗西。——为什么?
- Congratulations, Rosie. - What for?
我们学校举行了这次比赛，你是获胜者。
My school had this contest, and you are the winner.
你在开玩笑吧!我赢了什么?
You're kidding! What did I win?
你赢得了一张免费的前排票…今晚在美丽的克利夫兰市中心观看猫王的演唱会。
You won a free ticket, front row... To see Elvis Presley in concert tonight in beautiful downtown Cleveland.
——哦。——怎么了?
- Oh. - What's wrong?
你认为我可以把它换成汤姆·琼斯吗?
Do you think I could exchange it for Tom Jones?
我,我很抱歉。嗯…也许我会让我妹妹安妮去。
I, I'm sorry. Uh... Uh, maybe I'll let my sister Anne go instead.
她比我更喜欢猫王。
She likes Elvis better than I do.
不。你看，你不能……因为奖品的一部分就是你能亲眼见到猫王。
No. You see, you can't... Because part of the prize is that you get to meet Elvis Presley in person.
啊!那是整洁!我从没见过一个真正的名人是…哦!但是…嘿，有什么内幕?
Ah! That's neat! I never met a real celebrity be... Oh! But... Hey, what's the catch?
——抓?-是的。
- Catch? - Yeah.
当你赢得这些东西的时候总会有陷阱。
There's always a catch when you win these things.
托尼，你是从你老爸的药店买到乙醚的吗?以防。
Tony, did you get the ether from your old man's pharmacy? Just in case.
是啊，那家店关门后我偷偷溜进去的。
Yeah, I snuck in after the place closed.
布莱恩，你买到音乐会的票了吗?-是的，前排。
- Brian, did you get the concert tickets? - Yeah, front row.
我整晚都在排队，伙计。
I had to wait in line all night, man.
待在这里。我马上回来。
Stay here. I'll be right back.
格拉迪斯·普雷斯利死而复生了。
Gladys Presley has risen from the grave.
和你共度一夜。
One night with you.
这就是我现在祈祷的。
Is what I'm now prayin' for.
-托尼，帮我个忙，停车。-是的,当然。
- Tony, do me a favor, park the car. - Yeah, sure.
-就这样吗，约翰尼?我们在这里吗?-就是它了。我们在这里。
- Is this it, Johnny? We're here? - This is it. We're here.
我现在可以见到他了?
I get to meet him now, huh?
是的,很快。
Yeah, real soon.
我真希望我不用戴这假发。我喜欢金色的头发。
I wish I didn't have to wear this wig. I like my hair blonde.
我告诉过你。猫王喜欢深色头发的女人。
I told you before. Elvis loves women with dark hair.
还有这条裙子，太可怕了。
And this dress, it is horrible.
——它是蓝色的。猫王的最喜欢的颜色。——真的吗?
- It's blue. Elvis's favorite color. - Really?
是的。你没听过“蓝色麂皮鞋”这首歌吗?
Yeah. Haven't you ever heard of the song “blue suede shoes”?
是的。
Yeah.
对不起。我们能从这里通过吗?谢谢。
Sorry. Could we get through here? Thanks.
——对不起。我很抱歉。——谢谢。
- Excuse me. I'm sorry. - Thanks.
你没事吧?
You okay?
他在那儿!
There he is!
Satnin”。
Satnin'.
-我要出去。——为什么?
- I'm goin' out. - What for?
我想要一个芝士汉堡。
I want a cheeseburger.
-我去叫客房服务。-我不想要客房送餐汉堡。
- I'll call room service. - I don't want a room service burger.
我想要那种油腻的，就像你在咖啡店买到的那种……桌子上放着点唱机。
I want one of them greasy kinds, like you get in a coffee shop... With the little jukeboxes on the tables.
整个城市都知道你在这里。
The whole city knows you're here.
广播，电视，报纸上都有。你一出去，人们就会把你撕碎。
It's on the radio, TV, in the papers. You go out, people'll tear you up.
我要一个芝士汉堡!
I want a cheeseburger!
-我们会派人去拿一个。-我想出去买。
- We'll send somebody out for one. - I want to go out and get it.
我想坐在咖啡店里自己吃。
I want to sit down in the coffee shop and eat it myself.
我们可以像以前一样。我们下班后再去。
We can do like we always do. We'll go there after hours.
你可以独享整个咖啡店，包括油脂和所有东西。
You can have the whole coffee shop to yourself, grease and all.
我受够了这个地方只有我一个人!
I'm sick of havin' the place all to myself!
进来。
Come in.
西联汇款时间，e。"
Western union time, “e."
“亲爱的猫王:
“Dear Elvis:
祝克利夫兰成功出场。理查德。尼克松。”
Best wishes for a successful Cleveland appearance. Richard m. Nixon.”
好家伙不会忘记的，对吧?
Good ol' dick don't forget, does he?
没有,先生。
No, sir.
今晚不能来看你的演出了…“因为我妹妹出了车祸，现在在医院。
Can't come to your show tonight... “Because my sister got in a car accident and she's in the hospital.
我希望你做得很好。戴安娜人证都能用。”
I hope you do great. Diana cantinflas.”
-外面的世界很残酷，不是吗?-你说了" e "
- Cruel world out there, isn't it? - You said it, “e."
-有些事情看起来就是不公平。-从未说过更真实的话。
- Some things just don't seem fair. - Truer words “was” never spoken.
-送她一辆凯迪拉克。- - - - - -。
- Send her a Cadillac. - Right away.
我回来找你了，我的宝贝儿子。”
I've come back for you, my baby boy.”
可怜!
Have mercy!
“就像我一直告诉你的那样。
“Just like I always told you I would.
“爱和吻来自你的宝贝……Satnin。3
“Love and kisses from your precious... Satnin. III
Satnin”?那是谁?一些拉斯维加斯脱衣舞吗?
Satnin'? Who's that? Some Vegas stripper?
来吧,男人。他什么都不知道。
Come on, man. He don't know any better.
来吧,“e”。他不知道。
Come on, 'e.' He didn't know.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你在这里的时间还不够长，不知道。
You haven't been around long enough to know.
-知道吗，“e”?——Satnin”。他以前就是这么叫他妈妈的。
- Know what, “e”? - Satnin'. That's what he used to call his mama.
这有点像他对她的爱称。
It was kinda like his pet name for her.
女士们先生们，猫王时间到了。
Ladies and gentlemen, it's Elvis time.
猫王!猫王!猫王!
Elvis! Elvis! Elvis!
猫王!猫王!猫王!猫王!猫王!猫王!
Elvis! Elvis! Elvis! Elvis! Elvis! Elvis!
看这里,乔治。爱丽丝库珀。
Look here, George. Alice Cooper.
嗯。
Hmph.
也许我应该留长发，对吧?
Maybe I oughta grow my hair long, huh?
别再穿这些时髦的白色西装玩拉斯维加斯了。再一次震撼他们。
Stop wearin' these funky white suits and playin' Vegas. Really rock 'em again.
当然，如果你想失去你的观众。
Sure, man, if you want to lose your audience.
我的观众有死亡的危险。
My audience is in danger of dyin'.
-我想再为孩子们演奏一次。-你还有年轻粉丝。
- I wanna play for the kids again. - You still got young fans.
-他们坐在哪里?后排的?——地狱,“e”。
- Where do they sit? In the back row? - Hell, “e."
你不能冒这样的险。
You can't afford to take a chance like that.
当我破产的时候，我可以做任何我想做的事。
When I was broke, I could afford to do anything I wanted.
现在我是百万富翁了，什么事都干不起。
Now I'm a millionaire, can't afford to do a damn thing.
猫王!猫王!猫王!猫王!
Elvis! Elvis! Elvis! Elvis!
乔。
Jo.
显示时间。
Show time.
唷。唷。
Whew. Whew.
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my god!
没事的，我妈妈你没事的没事的，我妈妈不管你怎么做我妈妈，没事的没事的，我妈妈。
Well, that's all right, my mama that's all right with you that's all right, my mama any way you do my mama, all right that's all right that's all right, my mama.
你想怎么做都行。
Any way you wanna do.
好了，现在没事了，妈妈我没事了。
Well, that's all right now, mama that's all right with me.
没关系，我妈妈不管你怎么做。
That's all right, my mama any way you do.
妈妈，没事的，没事的。
Mama, that's all right that's all right.
没关系，我妈妈不管你怎么想，
That's all right, my mama any way you want to do,
没关系，我妈妈你想怎么做都行
that's all right, my mama any way that you wanna do that's all right
猫王!
Elvis!
智者说。
Wise men say.
只有傻瓜才会冲进去。
Only fools rush in.
但我帮不了你。
But I can't help.
爱上你。
Falling in love with you.
我要留下来。
Shall I stay.
这是一种罪过吗?
Would it be a sin.
因为我无能为力。
For I can't help.
坠入爱河。
Falling in love.
-罗西，起来。我们走吧。-和你一起-把花给他——花吗?
- Rosie, get up. Let's go. - With you, - give him the flowers. - The flowers?
像河流一样，一定会流向大海。
Like a river flows, surely to the sea.
亲爱的，就是这样。
Darling, so it goes.
有些事是命中注定的。
Some things are meant to be.
牵着我的手，也带走我的一生。
Take my hand, take my whole life too.
你看到猫王拿走花了吗?
Did you see Elvis take the flowers?
因为我情不自禁地坠入爱河。
For I can't help falling in love.
-和你一起-耶
- With you, - yeah!
因为我情不自禁地爱上了你
For I can't help falling in love with you
女士们,先生们…埃尔维斯已经离开了大楼。
Ladies and gentlemen... Elvis has left the building.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我们走吧。起来,起来,起来。
Let's go. Up, up, up.
是的,男人,是的。听起来就像摇滚乐。
Yeah, man, yeah. Sounds just like rock and roll to me.
好节目。
Good show.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
怎么了,男人吗?
What's wrong, man?
一文不值。什么事都没有。
Nothin'. Nothin' at all's wrong.
然后我的灵魂歌唱。
Then sings my soul.
我的救主上帝。
My savior god to thee.
你是多么伟大。
How great thou art.
-天啊，他不会出现的。——我们只想放松一下。
- Oh, man, he's never gonna show. - Just relax.
耶稣。
Jesus.
-他在那儿!-你确定吗?
- There he is! - Are you sure?
-绝对是他。——下来!
- That's definitely him. - Get down!
住下来!嘘。
Stay down! Shh.
-开车过去就行。——我要。保持冷静，好吗?
- Just drive up. - I'm gonna. Just stay calm, all right?
你是谁?
Who are you?
很高兴见到你，普雷斯利先生。
I'm happy to meet you, Mr. Presley.
——什么?——说“奶酪。”
- What? - Say “cheese.”
你好，普雷斯利先生。你好吗?
Hi, there, Mr. Presley. How are you?
-我叫约翰尼·沃尔夫。我来自俄亥俄州的泰勒。-到底怎么回事?
- My name is Johnny wolfe. I'm from Taylor, Ohio. - What the hell's goin' on?
什么都没有。我和我的朋友想知道你是否愿意来我家住几天。
Nothing. Me and my friends were wondering if you'd like to come to my house for a couple days.
-没人会伤害你的-把别人打扮成我妈的样子怎么样?
- No one's gonna hurt ya. - What's the idea dressin' somebody up like my mother?
-你是神经病吗?-不，我没有。
- You some kinda sicko or what? - No, I'm not.
-我想这是我能接近你的唯一方法。——你生病。
- I figured this was the only way I could get close to you. - You're sick.
-拜托，听我说一秒钟我的问题。-别挡我的路，孩子。
- Please, just listen to my problem for one second. - Get out of my way, son.
-请听我说，先生-我是认真的移动。
- Please, just listen to me, sir. - I mean it. Move.
——移动!——布莱恩,现在!
- Move! - Brian, now!
-世界卫生大会…-你在干什么?
- Wha... - What are you doing?
-好吧，嗯…-你在干什么?
- All, right, um... - What are you doing?
-把他抬上车。罗茜,进去。——不!
- Carry him in the car. Rosie, get in. - No!
上帝!你在干什么?你做了什么?
God! What are you doing? What have you done?
——哦,天哪!-没人会受伤的请,罗西。
- Oh, no! - No one's gonna get hurt. Please, Rosie.
——对不起!你没说过。-我知道我没这么说
- I'm sorry! You didn't say this. - I know I didn't say this.
这真的不是计划的一部分。
This is really not part of the package or anything.
-别伤害他。-别担心，罗西。
- Don't hurt him. - Don't worry, Rosie.
-警察会抓到我们的。-不会有警察介入的别担心。
- The police are gonna get us. - No police are gonna get involved. Don't worry.
一个很老的朋友。
A very old friend.
今天来过，因为他告诉镇上所有人…他刚刚找到的爱，原因是。
Came by today, 'cause he was telling everyone in town... Of the love that he'd just found, and the reason is.
对，我的理由是他的新恋情，哦，我的理由是……你们这些孩子逃不掉的。
Of his latest flame yeah, and my reason is of his latest flame, oh, and my reason is... You kids ain't gettin' away with this.
我要给艾布拉姆斯警长打电话。我要告发你们。
I'm calling sheriff Abrams. I'm turning you guys in.
——约翰的人。——呃,罗西?
- John, man. - Uh, Rosie?
什么?
What?
我告诉你。
I tell you what.
你不把我们交给警察…你妹妹安妮可能…镇上唯一能见到猫王的女孩。
You don't turn us in to the cops... And your sister Anne could be... The only girl in town who gets to meet Elvis Presley.
妈妈。
Mama.
她会很高兴的。
She'd really like that.
好吧。好吧，我会把嘴闭上的。
Okay. Okay, I'm gonna keep my mouth shut.
我今晚带她去酒店。
I'll bring her by the hotel tonight.
好吧?
Okay?
-来吧，来吧-没事的。
- Come on, come on. - It's all right.
重量减轻了。加油！加油
The weight is off. Come on, come on.
-我们在推吗?-不，他又滑倒了。
- Are we pushing? - No, he's slipping again.
-我的脚，我的脚-保罗，你得用力。
- My feet, my feet. - Paul, you gotta push.
当心!他的手臂!他的胳膊卡住了!
Look out! His arm! His arm got stuck!
推进。推进。
Push through. Push through there.
——把它!——好拍摄!
- Pull it! - Nice shot!
把他带到我家来。来吧。
Bring him to my house. Come on.
好吧,推。他就像一头死骡子。
All right, push. He's like a dead mule.
我试着”。他是slippin”!
I'm tryin'. He's slippin'!
保罗，你要用力。约翰,约翰!来吧。在里面。在里面。
Paul, you gotta push. John, John! Come on. Inside. Inside.
约翰尼!约翰尼,醒来。
Johnny! Johnny, wake up.
Pammie。
Pammie.
-是爸爸吗?——不。
- Is that dad? - Nah.
这是猫王。
It's Elvis Presley.
不可能。
No way.
嗯。
Mmm.
哇!
Wow!
你要拿他怎么办?
What're you gonna do with him?
我要把他交给妈妈。
I'm gonna give him to mom.
有点像“欢迎回家”的礼物。
Kinda like a “welcome home” gift.
我打赌比起我送她的耳环，她更喜欢他。
Bet she likes him more than the earrings I got her.
Pammie !
Pammie!
-该去教堂了。——未来。
- Time for church. - Coming.
别跟艾琳阿姨说这件事，好吗?
Don't say anything to aunt Irene about this, okay?
- Zip。- Zip。
- Zip. - Zip.
嗯?
Huh?
你。
You.
别挡道，孩子。
Outta my way, kid.
-我不想用这个-看这里。
- I don't want to have to use this. - Now, look here.
你现在放我出去，我就不会起诉你。
You let me out of here now, and I won't press charges.
-对不起，我不能。-你想要钱?
- I'm sorry, I can't. - You want money?
大概有5000个。这是你的。保留它。
I got about 5,000 there. It's yours. Keep it.
我不要你的钱。我只是需要你。
I don't want your money. I just need you.
我吗?为了什么?
Me? For what?
我的母亲。
My mother.
不要提到母亲。你让我更生气了。
Don't you mention mothers. You get me more pissed off.
-你耍了一个卑鄙的把戏，扰乱我的思想。——我很抱歉。它只是…我想既然你这么爱你妈妈，你应该能理解我的问题。
- That was a dirty trick you played, messin' with my mind. - I'm sorry. It's just... I figured that since you loved your mother so much, you could understand my problem.
-不要把时间花在别人的问题上。-我只是想让你和她谈谈。
- Don't have time for other people's problems. - I just want you to talk to her.
-带她去吃饭-我看起来像什么?数据输入器的服务吗?
- Take her to dinner. - What do I look like? A datin' service?
-你在和猫王说话。-我知道我在跟谁说话
- You're talking to Elvis Presley. - I know exactly who I'm talkin' to.
你是唯一能帮她的人。
You're the only person who can help her.
我还有五千万粉丝也这么说。
I got 50 million other fans that say the same thing.
git -现在!——是吗?你要对那些粉丝负责。
- Now git! - Yeah? Well, you've got a responsibility to those fans.
我有责任做唱片。
I've got a responsibility to make records.
如果你妈妈需要帮助，告诉她去买我的新专辑。
If your mother needs help, tell her to go buy my new album.
现在，扣动扳机。
Now, pull the trigger.
来吧，杀了我。来吧。猫王开枪。
Come on, shoot me. Come on. Shoot Elvis Presley.
来吧。我不会开枪的。
Come on. I'm not gonna shoot ya.
我不这么认为。
I didn't think so.
让我离开这里。
Let me get out of here.
所以有人带着问题来找你，你却不理他，对吧?
So someone comes to you with a problem and you turn your back on them, right?
就像你对待摇滚乐一样。
Just like you did with rock 'n' roll.
-我从来没有放弃过摇滚。——哦,不是吗?
- I never turned my back on rock 'n' roll. - Oh, no?
你没必要坐着看15次拉斯维加斯的盛世。
You didn't have to sit through viva Las Vegas 15 times.
我从没说过我的电影和摇滚有关。
I never said my movies had anything to do with rock 'n' roll.
你的演唱会怎么样?
How 'bout your concerts?
-我的演唱会太棒了-是吗如果你65岁。
- My concerts kick ass. - Yeah? If you're 65 years old.
-还有年轻粉丝。——在哪里?我没看到。我17岁。
- Still got young fans. - Where? I don't see any. I'm 17.
我这个年纪的人都不会买你的唱片。我这个年纪的人不会去听你的演唱会。
Nobody my age buys your records. Nobody my age goes to your concerts.
谁他妈想看一个人在舞台上腾跃……穿着白色连体衣唱着"共和国战歌" ?
Who the hell wants to see some guy prance around on stage... In a white jumpsuit singing “the battle hymn of the republic”?
开枪。我们可以去看爱丽丝·库珀唱《十八岁》
Shoot. We can go see Alice Cooper sing “eighteen.”
-哦，爱丽丝·库珀!-是的。
- Oh, Alice Cooper! - Yeah.
是啊，一个叫女孩名字的男人…在台上穿女人的内裤。
Yeah, a guy with a girl's name... Wears women's underwear onstage.
我听说他会把蛇的头咬下来。你喜欢那样，不是吗?
I hear he bites the heads off snakes. You'd like that, wouldn't you?
我没说他有多好，伙计。
I'm not saying he's any better, man.
我只是说他很酷。你曾经的样子。
I'm just saying he's cool. Something you used to be.
我可不是过去的样子，孩子。
I ain't no used-to-be, boy.
你在路上了，伙计。
You're on your way, man.
为什么?因为我给了人们他们想要的?
Why? 'Cause I give the people what they want?
完全正确。
Exactly.
-你在拍你曾经踢过的那个屁股。——基森的屁股吗?
- You're kissin' that same ass you used to kick. - Kissin' ass?
你以前是那种给别人不想要的东西的人。
You used to be the kind of guy who gave the people what they didn't want.
你今天为之效力的人…我在1956年被你吓死了。
The same people you play for today... Were scared to death of you in 1956.
你是个反叛者，伙计。牛逼。
You were a rebel, man. A bad-ass.
你是猫王。
You were Elvis.
你知道什么?
What do you know?
比上校要多得多。比和你一起玩的那些肥杂种多。地狱,是的。
A lot more than the colonel. More than those fat bastards you hang out with. Hell, yeah.
你上次跟我这样的人说话是什么时候?
When was the last time you even talked to somebody like me, huh?
俄亥俄中部某个无名小卒吗?
Some little fucking nobody in the middle of Ohio?
见鬼，伙计，你离开你的根太久了…你都不知道他们到底是什么。
Hell, man, you've been away from your roots so long... You don't even know what the hell they are.
你,嗯…你真的认为我失去了我的根吗?
You, uh... You really think I'm losing touch with my roots?
我是说，就一个晚上。
I'm saying, one night.
只一个晚上。那只是因为我不想感到内疚。
One night only. That's just 'cause I don't wanna feel guilty.
是的,上校。
Yeah, colonel.
是的。听着，我很抱歉就这么走了。
Yeah. Listen, I'm sorry I run off like that.
不,我……只是想理清思绪。
No, I... Just wanna clear my head.
开车转几天。我租了一辆车。
Drive around for a few days. I rented a car.
不，我不需要任何人陪伴。
No, I don't need any company.
没有，没有电话。你联系不上我。
No, there's no phone. You can't get in touch with me.
不,我知道。是的。周日在匹兹堡的音乐会。我就会与你同在。
No, I know. Yeah. The concert in Pittsburgh on Sunday. I'll be there.
好吧,再见。
All right, bye.
埃尔维斯，那是什么。代表什么?
Elvis, what's that “t.C.B.” thing stand for?
“处理公事。”
“Taking care of business.”
现在，我在哪里可以买到衣服?
Now, uh, where can I get some clothes?
呃，上楼吧。
Uh, come on upstairs.
-这些是你爸爸的衣服，对吧?——是的。
- These are your dad's clothes, huh? - Yep.
我和他一定差不多大。
Me and him must be about the same size.
-我以前在《56》里就是这么穿的——是的,男人。
- It's the way I used to dress back in "56." - Yeah, man.
我妈妈说你是56年最酷的。
My mama says you looked the coolest in '56.
-是吗?——是的,”56。
- She did, huh? - Yeah, '56.
——嗯。-除了…-我不知道，伙计什么是错的。-你在说什么?
- Hmm. - Except... - I don't know, man. Something's wrong. - What are you talkin' about?
我不知道。看起来不太对劲。
I don't know. It just doesn't look right.
-我觉得挺好的。-看起来很好，但有点不对劲。
- Looks fine to me. - Looks fine, but something's just not right.
你觉得这是什么?
What do you think it is?
——朋友。——哦,天哪!
- Buddy. - Oh, no!
- - - - - -来吧。-小修剪，是吧?
- Come on. - Little trim, huh?
也许可以把黑色染料洗掉?
Maybe wash the black dye out?
-你染了头发?——嗯…你有什么资格谈论风格?这叫什么?
- You dye your hair? - Well... Who are you to talk about style? What do you call this?
夹克。
Jacket.
-那是美国国旗!-是的，但是看起来很酷。
- That's an American flag! - Yeah, but it looks cool.
汗渍在条纹上，草渍在星星上。
Sweat on the stripes, and grass stains on the stars.
接下来是什么?国旗厕纸吗?
What's next, huh? Flag toilet paper?
——放松的人。这只是一件夹克。——这是可耻的。把它关掉。
- Relax, man. It's just a jacket. - It's disgraceful. Take it off.
-我不会脱下来的看起来太好了。-脱下来!
- I ain't gonna take it off. It looks too good. - Take it off!
在这里。
Here.
持有它。褶皱。
Hold it. Fold.
一次。
Again.
这个国家的年轻人，都快完蛋了。
The youth of this country, goin' straight to the dogs.
伙计，我为什么要用女士剃刀?
Man, how come I had to use a lady's razor?
我失去了我的。
I lost mine.
是的,对的。
Yeah, right.
-我妈妈回来了我在楼下等你。-当然，孩子。
- My mom's home. I'll meet you downstairs. - Yeah, sure, kid.
嗨。嗨,妈。欢迎回家。
Hi. Hi, ma. Welcome home.
你是想省电吗?这里太黑了!
Are you trying to save on electricity? It's dark in here!
我觉得会很浪漫。
I thought it might be romantic.
这地方一点都不浪漫。
There's nothing romantic about this place.
如果你去的话。
If you ever go.
亲爱的，我会很孤独
Darlin', I'll be oh so lonely
我会感到悲伤和忧郁。
I'll be sad and blue.
对你哭泣。
Cryin over you.
亲爱的只会乞讨和偷窃。
Dear only would beg and steal.
只为感受你温暖的心跳靠近我。
Just to feel your warm heart beat close to mine.
如果你去的话。
If you ever go.
亲爱的，我会的。
Darlin', I'll be oh.
所以孤独。
So lonely.
跪下求我。
Beggin' on my knees.
我只要求你。
All I ask is please.
请爱我。
Please love me.
神圣的狗屎!
Holy shit!
你做……约翰尼?
What're you do... Johnny?
妈，你在干什么?
Ma, what are you doing?
——这是他。他在这里!-我知道是他。
- It's him. He's here! - I know it's him.
-他在我们家!-你能冷静一下吗?
- He's in our house! - Would you calm down?
-但我还没准备好我还没准备好。——放松。
- But I'm not ready. I'm not ready at all. - Relax.
但是，但是，但是，他从哪里来?他是怎么来的?
But, but, but, where did he come from? How did he get here?
-我带他来的-你没有。
- I brought him here. - You did not.
看看我的头发，简直是一团糟。天啊，没化妆。
Look at my hair, it's a wreck. Oh, god, no make-up.
一条裙子。我需要一条裙子。
A dress. I need a dress.
我已经两年多没买过裙子了。
I haven't bought a dress in over two years.
-等一下。约翰尼，怎么样?-你的婚纱?
- Wait a minute. Johnny, how's this, huh? - Your wedding gown?
-太多了，是吧?——小。
- Too much, huh? - A little.
我该怎么办?我该穿什么啊?
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna wear, huh?
-他是怎么来的?-我叫他来的。
- How did he get here anyway? - I asked him to come here.
他就这样来了?
And he came just like that?
-我不得不强迫他。-你强迫他?
- I kinda had to force him. - You forced him?
-我和伙计们，我们不得不强迫他…-违背他的意愿?
- Well, me and the guys, we had to force him to get... - Against his will?
-是的。-你做那样的事会惹上麻烦的。
- Yeah. - You could get in trouble for doing something like that.
-你不该这么做!-我是为了你。
- You should not have done it! - I was doing it for you.
我不管你是为谁做的。这不是正确的。
I don't care who you did it for. It wasn't right.
-好吧，我下去告诉他可以走了…-哦,不。不,等等,等等。
- Fine, I'll go down and tell him he can leave... - Oh, no. No, wait, wait.
听着，既然他来了，我是说，他至少可以留下来吃晚饭。
Listen, now that he's here, I mean, he could at least stay for dinner.
正确的。
Right.
我不管你要怎么做。你下楼把他留在这里。
I don't care what you have to do. You go downstairs and keep him here.
好的，你说对了。
Right, you got it.
掷骰子。一，二，三，四，五。
Roll the dice. One, two, three, four, five.
-伙计，我打赌这是一艘梦幻之船。——无用!
- Man, I'll bet it's a dream boat. - Dud!
——走吧。-开始了。
- Go. - Here we go.
-你是黑发的那个。-哦,是的。
- You're the brunette. - Oh, yeah.
我当然是。
Of course I am.
很高兴见到你，普雷斯利先生。
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. Presley.
,嗯…欢迎你到我们家来。
And, uh... Welcome you to our home.
嗯,你可以…你可以叫我猫王。
Well, you can... You can call me Elvis.
猫王。
Elvis.
当然可以。猫王。哦,我的上帝。
Of course. Elvis. Oh, my god.
-我希望你不介意芝士汉堡。——嗯…-不，女士，它们很好。谢谢你！-哦,好的。
- I hope you don't mind cheeseburgers. - Well... - No, ma'am, they're just fine. Thank you. - Oh, good.
这些年来，我一直想着这一刻……还有终于见到你，请你来吃晚餐是什么感觉。
All these years I've been thinking about this moment... And what it'd be like to finally meet you and have you over for dinner.
我有很多问题想问你…我现在一个也想不出来。
I had so many questions I wanted to ask you... And I can't think of a single one now.
我记得你想知道一些关于猫王的事。
I remember something you wanted to know about Elvis.
什么?
What?
-我听到你问艾琳阿姨的事-怎么了，亲爱的?
- Something I heard you asking aunt Irene about. - What was it, honey?
你想知道猫王的床技是否也一样好…因为他擅长唱歌。
You wondered if Elvis was as good in bed... As he was at singing.
我的上帝。
My god.
强尼，去开门。帕姆!
Johnny, get the door. Pam!
-强尼，他在哪?我的妹妹安妮。——嗨,罗西。这是怎么呢
- Johnny, where is he? My sister Anne. - Hi, Rosie. What's going on?
我告诉过你我会带她过来。
I told you I was bringing her by.
——我很抱歉。-愿上帝发发慈悲。
- I'm sorry. - The lord have mercy.
——看!他就在这里。安妮,他。-我想看看这个。
- Look! There he is. Anne, that's him. - I wanna take a look at this.
罗西!
Rosie!
怎么了,伙计们?
What's up, guys?
-你好吗?看，这是谢丽尔。-嘿，嘿，嘿!
- How you doing? Look, this is Cheryl. - Hey, hey, hey!
和朱迪。这是麦斯特汉堡的。
And Judy. They're from meister burger.
-很高兴见到你。-他们会跟我们出去的，如果…-请给我们介绍一下猫王。-加油，伙计们!
- Pleased to meet you. - They'd go out with us if... - If you could introduce us to Elvis. - Come on, guys!
——谢谢你,小伙子。-你欠我们一个人情。猫王,老兄!
- Thanks, man. - You owe us one. Elvis, buddy!
嘿,怎么了?
Hey, what's up?
-嗨，艾琳阿姨。——哦,天哪。这太大了!
- Hey, aunt Irene. - Oh, gosh. This is so big!
上帝,他是美丽的。
God, he's beautiful.
艾琳。
Irene.
嘿,发生了什么?这是我叔叔的波尔卡乐队。
Hey, what's happening? This is my uncle's polka band.
我告诉他关于猫王的事。我想他们可能会被发现。
I told him about Elvis. I figured they might get discovered.
这更像是一个啤酒节。
It's more like an oktoberfest.
天呐
Holy shit.
罗西,走了。
Go, Rosie, go.
自从你爸来过之后，我还没见过这么热闹。
I haven't seen it this lively since your dad was around.
既然大家都来了，不如带他们去舞厅吧?
Since everybody's here, why don't you bring 'em in the ballroom?
我去买些薯片，给你办一个真正的欢迎回家的派对。
I'll get some chips and throw you a real welcome-home party.
-好主意。快点回来。——好的。
- That's a great idea. Hurry back. - Okay.
是对的,那就去做。是的,是的。
Right, do it. Yeah, yeah.
把它带回家，宝贝!
Take it home, baby!
——嗨,普里西拉。——嘿,史蒂夫。
- Hi, Priscilla. - Hey, Steve.
——什么?——朋友。
- What? - Buddy.
-你好,约翰。
-Hi, John.
来吧。
Come on.
我猜他今晚不想打架，是吗?
I guess he don't feel much like fightin' tonight, does he?
-我想没有。——朋克。
- I guess not. - Punk.
晚安,约翰。
Good night, John.
我想打破这个，好吗?
I wanna break this one, all right?
-你不关灯睡觉吗?-不，她睡觉的时候戴着。
- Aren't you gonna turn your lights out and go to sleep? - No, she sleeps with them on.
哦!黏糊糊的灵魂吸吮者，是吧?
Oh! Slimy soul suckers, huh?
你知道他们吗?
You know about 'em?
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
我的小女儿丽莎开着灯睡觉，我不知道要保护自己多久。
My little girl Lisa slept with her lights on for I don't know how long to protect herself.
所以你不认为我疯了?
So you don't think I'm crazy?
疯了吗?不。那些东西是杀手。
Crazy? No. Those things are killers.
像你这样的小女孩得小心他们。
Little girl like you's gotta watch out for 'em.
这就是我一直想告诉这里所有人的…但是没有人会听。
That's what I've been trying to tell everyone here... But no one will listen.
嗯,我会的。
Well, I will.
你看，问题是……人们有点被误导了……关于那些黏糊糊的吸魂者。
You see, the thing is... People are a little misinformed... About the slimy soul suckers.
——误导?-是的。
- Misinformed? - Yeah.
他们认为黏糊糊的吸血鬼只能杀死…当灯熄灭的时候。
They think that slimy soul suckers can only kill... When the lights are out.
但是，这并不是真的。
And, well, that just ain't true.
——不是吗?——没有。
- It isn't? - No.
当灯亮着的时候，黏糊糊的灵魂吸盘也能杀了你。
Slimy soul suckers can kill ya when the lights are on too.
——他们可以吗?-是的。
- They can? - Yeah.
我现在该怎么办?
What am I gonna do now?
现在，有办法打败他们了。
Well now, there's a way to beat 'em.
但你要坚强。
But you gotta be tough.
你严厉吗?
Are you tough?
也许吧。我该怎么做呢?
Maybe. Uh, what do I have to do?
每天晚上睡觉前，你要关掉一盏灯。
Each night before you go to sleep, you turn out one light.
然后第二天晚上，你关了两盏灯。
And then the next night, you turn out two lights.
如此下去，直到所有的灯都熄灭。
And so on until all the lights are out.
那时候黏糊糊的吸血鬼就会知道了。
And that's when the slimy soul suckers will know.
知道吗?
Know what?
你不害怕。
That you're not afraid.
你看，他们不能忍受那些不害怕的小女孩。
You see, they can't stand little girls that aren't afraid.
-哦，它们会飞走的，再也不会回来了。——真的吗?
- Oh, they'll take off, they'll never come back. - Really?
为我的小女儿工作。她的灯一熄灭…
Worked for my little girl. Soon as her lights were off..
那些黏糊糊的吸血鬼再也没回来。
The slimy soul suckers never came back.
——哇。-这样吧。
- Wow. - Tell you what.
让我们从这个开始。
Let's start with that one right over there.
-你说呢?-把它关掉?
- What do you say? - Uh, turn it out?
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
我们就不能从这个开始吗?
Couldn't we start with that one?
你到底想不想打败他们?
You wanna beat these guys or not?
好姑娘。
Good girl.
那就这样吧。
There you go.
一个下来。
One down.
晚上,亲爱的。
Night, sweetie.
嗯…哦!
Um... oh!
哦,我的上帝!约翰尼!
Oh, my god! Johnny!
你知道吗，他早就该回来了。
You know, he should've been back a long time ago.
-他去哪了?-我不知道。
- Where'd he go? - I don't know.
他说他要去派对商店，但那就在几英里外。
He said he was going to the party store, but that's a few miles away.
你不担心。我去看看他，好吗?
Don't you worry. I'll go check on him, all right?
别担心。等待在这里。
Don't worry. Wait right here.
埃尔维斯离开舞厅了。
Elvis has left the ballroom.
嘿，孩子，进城怎么走?
Hey, kid, which way to town?
沿着这条路一直走。
Straight down the road.
我能用一下你的自行车吗?-当然，猫王。
- Can I use your bike? - Yeah, sure, Elvis.
打破它，燃烧它。
Break it, burn it.
到处拖着它。
Drag it all around.
扭它，扭它你不能把它弄下来，因为每一分钟每一小时。
Twist it, turn it you can't tear it down 'cause every minute every hour.
你会被这种奇怪而强大的力量所震撼……我的爱
You'll be shaken by the strange and mighty power... Of my love
嘿,猫王。
Hey, Elvis.
嘿，孩子，你怎么了?
Hey, kid, what happened to you?
-我跟人打架了-你没事吧?
- I got in a fight. - You all right?
-我很好。-看来你输了。
- Yeah, I'm fine. - Looks like you lost.
没有大便。
No shit.
-我想你没从我的电影中学到什么。——嗯?
- I guess you didn't learn anythin' from watchin' my movies. - Huh?
在我拍摄的几乎所有照片中，我都在打架，而且我总是赢。
In almost all my pictures I get in a fight, and I always win.
这个问题有点棘手，伙计。
Well, this one was kind of tough, man.
-是四个人对我。-有一次他们9个人联合起来对付我。
- It was four guys against me. - I had nine of 'em gang up on me once.
-打遍了所有人-这不是电影，伙计
- Whupped every one of 'em. - This isn't the movies, man.
如果出现这种情况，我会和他们中最厉害的人一起踢屁股。
If the situation arose, I'd kick ass with the best of 'em.
正确的。只要有人喊"行动"
Right. As long as somebody was yelling “action.”
我要走了。
I'm out of here.
-你得回家了你妈妈担心死了。——猫王?
- You need to get on home. Your mama's worried sick. - Elvis?
是吗?
Yeah?
你很了解女人，是吧?
You know a lot about women, don't ya?
孩子，在我把她们变成女人之前，她们都只是女孩。
Well, son, they're all just girls until I turn 'em into women.
-是的。我想这就是为什么也许你能帮我。-当然，有什么问题吗?
- Yeah. Well, I figure that's why maybe you can help me. - Sure, what's the problem?
这个女孩。她的名字叫贝斯。
There's this girl. Her name's Beth.
她住在那里，而且…我真想走到她面前，约她出去。
She lives up there, and... I want so badly just to go up to her and ask her on a date.
但是…不要告诉任何人。
But... don't say anything to anybody.
我不知道。我…我很害怕。
I don't know. I'm... I'm scared.
你在怕什么?
What are you scared of?
她是个…我不知道。我配不上她。
Well, that she's a g... I don't know. That I'm not good enough for her.
大便。见鬼，伙计，你根本不知道这是什么感觉。
Shit. Hell, man, you don't know what the hell this feels like.
哦，是的，我喜欢。
Oh, yes, I do.
你觉得我为什么花那么多时间在吉他上?
Why do you think I spent so much time with my guitar?
-吉他不能拒绝。-是的。
- Guitar can't say no. - Yeah.
但后来我发现了这个秘密。
But then I discovered the secret.
比爱情药水好。我找到了你想要的任何女孩的钥匙。
Better than a love potion. I found the key to gettin' any girl you want.
那是什么?
What's that?
——信心。——信心?
- Confidence. - Confidence?
一旦我有了信心，我就有了女朋友。
Once I got confidence, I got girls.
你有女孩，因为你是猫王。"
You got girls "cause you're Elvis Presley."
不，孩子，女歌手比畅销唱片早。
No, son, the ladies came before the hit records.
不,诚实的。女人喜欢的信心。
No, honest. Women love confidence.
你把自己打扮得漂漂亮亮……擦亮你的鞋子，买一大束花。
You slick yourself up... Shine your shoes, get a nice big bouquet of flowers.
只要有信心，就能爬上那座山，敲开那扇门……那会让那个小女孩疯狂地爱上你的。
And just the confidence it takes to march up that hill and knock on that door... That'll make that little girl fall crazy in love with you.
你这样认为吗?
You think so?
我知道。
I know so.
的信心。是的。
Confidence. Yeah.
Oh-ho-ho。可能是火花塞的问题。
Oh-ho-ho. It's probably the spark plug.
-这是全新的——是吗?你知道的，他们有时会崩溃。
- It's a brand-new one. - Yeah? Well, they give out sometimes, you know.
让我给她一次机会，好吗?
Let me give her a shot, huh?
-这需要温柔的抚摸，你知道的。-是的。
- It takes a gentle touch, you know. - Yeah.
你介意吗?
You mind?
哦，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝。
Oh, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby booma, booma, booma.
宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，回来吧，宝贝，我想和你过家家，好吧，你可能会去上大学你可能会去上学，你可能会有一辆粉红色的凯迪拉克但你不要做任何人的傻瓜
Ba by, baby, baby, ba by, baby, baby, come back, baby I wanna play house with you, well, you may go to college you may go to school, you may have a pink Cadillac but don't you be nobody's fool
现在，宝贝回来，宝贝娃娃。
now, baby come back, baby doll.
回来吧，宝贝。
Come back, baby doll.
回来吧，宝贝，我想和你一起过家家，让我告诉你，宝贝。
Come back, baby, I wanna play house with you and listen let me tell you, baby.
我在说什么。
What I'm talkin' about.
回到我身边，小姑娘，我们可以过家家，现在，宝贝回来，宝贝娃娃。
Come on back to me, little girl, so we can play some house, now, baby come back, baby doll.
回来吧，宝贝。
Come back, baby doll.
回来吧，宝贝，我想和你过家家，我想过家家。
Come back, baby I wanna play house with you, I wanna play house.
来吧。
Come on.
-我们要去哪?-我们去购物
- Where we goin'? - We're goin' shoppin'
-我们要去购物?猫王!-是的。
- we're going shopping? Elvis! - Yeah.
-他们没认出我来。——嗯。
- They didn't recognize me. - Uh-uh.
看这里。没人认识我!
Look here. Nobody's recognizing me!
我已经15年没能做到了。
I haven't been able to do this for 15 years.
我能为您效劳吗?
May I help you?
-是的，我们要了。-哦，当然。哪一项?
- Yeah, we'll take it. - Oh, of course. Which item?
这一切。一切。
All of it. Everything.
——啊。交货日期吗?——明天早上。
- Ah. Delivery date? - Tomorrow morning.
哦,我很抱歉。我们需要10天交货。
Oh, I'm sorry. We require ten days for delivery.
-你知道你在跟谁说话吗?——没有。
- You know who you're talkin' to? - No.
我是猫王。
I'm Elvis Presley.
我是恩格尔伯特·汉珀丁克。
And I'm Engelbert Humperdinck.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
我们会去一家你想要什么就送什么的商店。
We'll go to a store where they deliver things when you want 'em.
有钱能使鬼推磨
Money talks.
宝贝，有件事我想让你知道。
Well, this is one thing, baby that I want you to know.
来吧，让我们玩一个小房子，我们可以像以前一样好吧，宝贝回来，宝贝娃娃。
Come on back and let's play a little house and we can act like we did before well, baby come back, baby doll.
回来吧，宝贝。
Come back, baby doll.
回来吧，宝贝，我想和你过家家，哦，回来吧，宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝，宝宝。
Come back, baby I wanna play house with you, oh, come back baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby booma, booma, booma.
宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，回来吧，宝贝，我想和你过家家
Ba by, baby, baby, ba by, baby, baby, come back, baby I wanna play house with you,
你好,约翰。-你好，德弗罗医生。你好吗?
- Hiya, John. - Hiya, Dr. Devereaux. How are you?
我在想我能不能见一下贝丝。
I was wondering if I could possibly see Beth for a moment.
嗯,你看,约翰。
Um, look, John.
你看起来是个好孩子。这与个人无关。
You seem like a good kid. And this is nothing personal.
但你现在的情况不太好。
But things aren't going too well for you right now.
这种气氛对贝丝来说不健康。
And that's not a healthy atmosphere for Beth.
你明白吗?
Do you understand?
你能帮我把这些给贝丝吗?
Do you mind giving these to Beth for me?
它们对我没什么用。
I don't have much use for 'em.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
哦,嗨,约翰尼!
Oh, hi, Johnny!
嗨,约翰!-他来了。你觉得怎么样?
- Hi, John! - There he is. Well, what do you think?
我以为你只是想把事情解决一下。
Well, I thought you were just gonna fix things up a bit.
我不知道你会改变一切。
I didn't know you were gonna change everything.
这些东西都是今天送来的。我给你准备了一些惊喜。来吧。
All this stuff got here today. I got some surprises for you. Come on.
-上楼吧。——惊喜?
- Come on upstairs. - Surprises?
你重新装修了我整个房间?
You redecorated my whole room?
-我在这里睡不着。——为什么不呢?
- I can't sleep in here. - Why not?
我会醒来成为liberace。
I'll wake up and be liberace.
约翰尼。
Johnny.
任何一个孩子都想要这样的房间。
Any kid would kill to have a room like this.
我的桌子怎么了?我的床和海报呢?
What happened to my desk? Where's my bed and my posters?
他们都在后面。我把它们扔了。
They're all out back. I threw em out.
你可以把这里变成恩赐之地，我不在乎。
You can turn the rest of this place into Graceland, I don't care.
但我要把我的东西拿回来。
But I'm getting my stuff back.
约翰尼。
Johnny.
——约翰尼。——哦,男人。
- Johnny. - Oh, man.
-约翰尼，回来。——这是什么?
- Johnny, come back. - What's this?
我在跟你说话，强尼。
I'm talking to you, Johnny.
哦!
Oh!
看看这张海报，伙计。这完全是毁了。
Look at this poster, man. It's totally ruined.
-你不会想挂那种乐队的海报的。——为什么不呢?
- You don't wanna be hangin' up posters of them kind of bands. - Why not?
他们中有一半是撒旦崇拜者。
Half of 'em are Satan worshipers.
这就是查理·曼森砍人的时候听的音乐。
That's the kind of music Charlie manson was listenin' to when he hacked up those people.
你听说过有人听了“惊慌失措”就犯下大屠杀吗?
You ever hear of anybody listen to “all shook up” and committin' mass murder?
你疯了。你知道吗?
You're crazy. You know that?
——上帝!我怎么可能听你的?-你在说什么?
- God! How could I ever listen to you, huh? - What are you talkin' about?
你说我可以爬上那座山的。你说过一切都会解决的。
You told me I could go up that hill. You said everything would work out.
但我早该知道。为什么现在会有什么不同呢?
But I should've known better. Why should anything be different now?
我是说，我的音乐在学校格格不入。
I mean, my music doesn't fit in at school.
我和我喜欢的女孩合不来。
I don't fit in with the girl I like.
我甚至都不适应自己的家。
I don't even fit in in my own home.
——约翰尼?约翰尼?-不，不，让他走让他走。
- Johnny? Johnny? - No, no, let him go. Let him go.
让他发泄一下。来吧。
Let him blow off a little steam. Come on.
停止。
Stop.
你好。
Howdy.
你妈妈告诉我你被才艺表演除名了。
Your mama told me you got cut from the talent show.
她说这对你很重要。
She said it meant a lot to you.
我只是想进来帮你唱歌。
I just thought maybe I'd come in here and help you with your song.
-给你看看舞步。-我的动作怎么了?
- Show you some moves. - What's wrong with the way I move?
你裤子里没有火啊。
Well, you got no fire in your pants.
你腰部以下已经死了。
You're just dead from the waist down.
正确的。他想让我们塞裤子，扭屁股……为了让一群蓝发女士尖叫。
Right. He wants us to stuff our pants and wiggle our asses... To make a bunch of blue-haired ladies scream.
- - - - - -来吧。-我没塞裤子。上帝这样做。
- Come on. - Well, I didn't stuff my pants. God did that.
如果你对那些蓝头发的女士们置之不理也就是你的一部分观众，你永远也出不了这个车库。
And if you go turnin' your back on those blue-haired ladies... Which is part of your audience, you're never gonna get out of this garage.
正确的。那你要教我们什么?如何做你自己?
Right. And what're you gonna teach us, huh? How to be you?
如何玩维加斯?来吧,男人。
How to play Vegas? Come on, man.
你都快40岁了。你所知道的关于摇滚的一切都是乱世佳人。
You're almost 40 years old. Everything you knew about rock 'n' roll is gone with the wind.
我也是。
Me too.
你疯了吗?拒绝国王的免费建议?
Are you crazy? Turning down free advice from the king himself?
他不是国王。
He's not the king.
不了。
Not anymore.
史蒂夫,这是他。
Steve, that's him.
-那是猫王!——哦。
- That's Elvis Presley! - Aw.
不可能。猫王有一头黑头发。
No way. Elvis has black hair.
-莫妮卡那天晚上在派对上看到他了。-绝对是他。
- Monica saw him at the party the other night. - It's definitely him.
我告诉你，就是他。
I'm telling you, it's him.
如果是他，也许他会给我们唱首歌。
If it's him, then maybe he'll sing us a little song.
-史蒂夫，别这样。——不。
- Steve, come on. - Don't.
只是找点乐子，宝贝。
Just having a little fun, babe.
嘿,你!嘿,鬓角。
Hey, you! Hey, sideburns.
那边有个小妞想听你唱首歌。
I got a little chick over there wants to hear you sing a song.
噢,是吗?周日带她去匹兹堡听我的演唱会吧?
Oh, yeah? Why don't you bring her to my concert in Pittsburgh on Sunday?
-你不会害怕吧?-我没那么说，对吧?
- You ain't scared, are ya? - I didn't say that, did I?
-史蒂夫，你惹的麻烦已经够多了。-你为什么不闭嘴?
- Steve, you've caused enough trouble. - Why don't you shut up?
嘿,嘿!我会唱歌。
Hey, hey! I'll sing.
——是吗?-是的。
- Yeah? - Yeah.
在这里。
Here.
你什么都不用担心。
Don't you worry about a thing.
准备好了，开始吧，伙计，开始吧我有一个我爱的女孩所以我准备好了，准备好了，准备好了。
Ready, set go, man, go I got a gal that I love so I'm ready ready, ready, ready I'm ready.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪我准备好了，准备好了，泰迪我准备好了，准备好了，准备好了。
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready, ready, ready, Teddy I'm ready, ready, ready to rock 'n' roll.
去街角捡我的甜心派。
Going to the corner pick up my sweetie pie.
她是我的摇滚宝贝，她是我眼中的苹果。
She's my rock 'n' roll baby she's the apple of my eye.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪我准备好了。
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready.
准备好，准备好，我准备好了。
Ready, ready, ready I'm ready.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪，我准备好了，准备好摇滚所有的平顶猫和工装裤娃娃。
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready, ready to rock 'n' roll all the flattop cats and the dungaree dolls.
都要去体育馆参加袜子舞舞会。
Are headed for the gym to the sock-hop ball.
这地方真热闹，猫都疯了。
The joint's really jumpin' the cats are goin' wild.
音乐真的让我着迷我喜欢那种疯狂的风格我准备好了，准备好了，泰迪我准备好了。
The music really sends me I dig that crazy style I'm ready, ready, ready Teddy I'm ready.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪我准备好了。
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪，我准备好了，准备好摇滚了
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready, ready to rock 'n' roll
所有的平底猫和工装裤娃娃。
All the flattop cats and the dungaree dolls.
都要去体育馆参加袜子舞舞会。
Are headed for the gym to the sock-hop ball.
这地方真热闹，猫都疯了。
The joint's really jumpin' the cats are goin' wild.
音乐真的让我着迷我喜欢那种疯狂的风格我准备好了，准备好了，泰迪我准备好了。
The music really sends me I dig that crazy style I'm ready, ready, ready Teddy I'm ready.
准备好，准备好，我准备好了。
Ready, ready, ready I'm ready.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪，我准备好了，准备好摇滚了。
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready, ready to rock 'n' roll.
脱掉我的鞋子卷起我褪色的牛仔裤。
Kick off my shoes roll up my faded jeans.
带上我的摇滚宝贝，来学校吧。
Grab my rock 'n' roll baby come on to school.
洗牌到左边洗牌到右边&
Shuffle to the left shuffle to the right &
我准备好了，准备好了，准备好了，我准备好了。
& gonna rock and roll till the early, early light I'm ready ready, ready, ready I'm ready.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪我准备好了。
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready.
准备好了，准备好了，泰迪，我准备好了，准备好摇滚了。
Ready, ready Teddy I'm ready, ready to rock 'n' roll.
你还不错，鬓角男。
You ain't half bad, sideburns.
我问你个问题。你是做什么的?
Let me ask you somethin'. What do you do for a livin'?
我经营一家汽车商店。
I manage an auto shop.
是吗?通常我唱歌是有报酬的。
Yeah? Well, I usually get paid for singin' as a rule.
所以我觉得你现在应该为我做你所做的。
So I figure now you ought to do what you do for me.
外面有辆车需要一套新的座套。
There's a car sittin' outside needs a new set of seat covers.
确定。你想要什么颜色的?
Sure. What color do you want?
我猜他是黄色的。
I figure his color is yellow.
皱纹在我的脸上和手上形成。
Lines form on my face and hands.
好了，大家都出去，除了你。你得待在车里。
Okay, everybody out, except you. You got to stay in the car.
你们经常打架吗?
Do you always get in fights?
我也无能为力了。有时候人们就是想打架。
Not any more than I can help it. Sometimes people just want to fight.
——你明白吗?-是的。
- You okay? - Yeah.
——嘿,猫王?——是吗?
- Hey, Elvis? - Yeah?
我的一首歌出了点问题。
I was having a little problem with one of my songs.
给我表演几招?
Show me some moves?
为什么,当然。我很乐意。
Why, sure. I'll be glad to.
万能的主啊，感受我的体温升高
Lord almighty feel my temperature risin'
越烧越高，烧穿了我的鞋底。
higher, higher it's burnin' through to my soles.
一个,两个……三、四……5、6……7、8。
One, two... Three, four... Five, six... Seven, eight.
现在慢慢来。两个。和去。
Now around real slow. Two. And go.
来吧，像这样绕过去。再试一次。
Go ahead, 'round like that. Try it again.
慢慢来。一件容易的事。
Come around real slow. Easy.
就是这样。最后折断你的臀部。
That's it. Snap your hip at the end.
-还不错。——我的手吗?
- Not too bad. - My hands?
手放松。在这样的。
Hands are relaxed. Around like that.
两个,四个。
Two, and four.
——好。这是好的。-说得不错。
- Fine. That was good. - That was a good one.
那就这样吧。
There you go.
-嘿，你好吗?——好。我今晚在餐厅看到你了。
- Hey, how are ya? - Fine. I saw you at the diner tonight.
我想和你谈谈。
I wanted to talk to you.
我也想和你谈谈。
I kinda wanted to talk to you too.
我父亲的事我很抱歉。
I'm sorry about my father.
他以为他能掌控我的生活，但他做不到。
He thinks he can run my life, but he cant.
别担心。
Don't worry about that.
你想跟埃尔维斯谈谈吗，或者想要个签名?
Listen, you wanna talk to Elvis, or maybe get an autograph?
不。
No.
我想和你谈谈。
I wanna talk to you.
你想出去走走吗?
Uh, you wanna take a walk?
-是的。-好吧，我们走。
- Yeah. - All right, let's go.
-外面冷吗?在这里。-是的。谢谢。
- Is it cold out? Here. - Yeah. Thanks.
继续。把它出来。
Go on. Turn it out.
-这会杀了他们的，对吧?-哦,是的。
- This'll kill 'em, right? - Oh, yeah.
-这能彻底摆脱他们吗?-一劳永逸。
- This'll get rid of them once and for all? - Once and for all.
我不能。
I can't.
好吧,没关系。
Well, that's okay.
我想我只是让你知道你有更多的勇气。
I guess I just had you figured for havin' more guts than that.
——晚安。——晚安。
- Good night. - Good night.
猫王?
Elvis?
是吗?
Yeah?
这是我的女孩!
That's my girl!
你好,马。
Hiya, ma.
约翰尼,我只是……我只想说谢谢。
Johnny, I just... I just wanna say thanks.
你把他带到这里的机会。
You know, the chance you took in bringing him here.
从来没有人为我做过这样的事。
Nobody's ever done anything like that for me.
我只是觉得你值得我这么做。
Well, I just figured that you were worth it.
——嘿,你看。看。到这里来。——什么?
- Hey, look. Look. Come here. - What?
帕姆家的灯熄了。
Pam's lights are out.
哦，你真了不起，普雷斯利先生。
Oh, you are something, Mr. Presley.
-大家都知道你在这里。-你们出去。我来对付人群。
- Everybody knows you're here. - You guys get out. I'll take care of the crowd.
——走吧。- - - - - -来吧。
- Let's go. - Come on.
我知道一个地方我们可以去。他们不会找到我们的。
I know a place we can go. They'll never find us.
——在哪里?你会划船吗?
- Where's that? - Can you row a boat?
我能行吗?你没看到克里奥尔国王吗?
Can I row? Didn't you see king creole?
你们去哪儿了?
Where were you guys?
嗯，我们在湖上划了划艇。
Well, we went on a rowboat ride on the lake.
啊，划船?是啊，我妈喜欢划船。
Ah, a rowboat ride? Yeah, my mom loves those rowboat rides.
——约翰尼!——倾听。说真的,猫王。
- Johnny! - Listen. Seriously, Elvis.
你得离开这里。
You gotta get outta here.
外面有一大群人，而且越来越多。
There's a crowd of people out front, and it's gettin' bigger.
我有个主意。这就是我们摆脱那些人的方法。
I got an idea. This is how we can get rid of those people.
打扰一下!如果你来过这里…要去看埃尔维斯·普雷斯利，你会有更好的机会……今晚能见到他。
Excuse me! If you came here... To see Elvis Presley, you'd stand a better chance... Of seeing him tonight.
他要在肯尼迪高中的才艺表演上表演。
He's performing at the Kennedy high school talent show.
很快就卖光了。
They're selling out real fast.
-你真的在参加才艺表演，是吗?——是的。
- You're really playing the talent show, huh? - Yep.
你打算怎么办?让整个乐团都飞起来?
What are you gonna do? Fly in your whole orchestra?
嗯。你和你的乐队要支持我。
Uh-uh. You and your band are gonna back me up.
——我的乐队吗?——是的。
- My band? - Yep.
没办法,男人。我们被淘汰了。
No way, man. We got cut from that show.
他们不喜欢我们。那些人讨厌摇滚。
They don't like us. And those guys hate rock 'n' roll.
-他们讨厌摇滚，对吧?——嗯。
- They hate rock 'n' roll, huh? - Mm-hmm.
这样就更有趣了，不是吗?
That'll just make it more fun, won't it?
现在打电话给你的人。我们还有工作要做。
Now call your boys. We got some work to do.
——T.c.b。?-是的。T.C.B.
- T.c.b., right? - Yeah. T.C.B.
我听说今晚有很棒的摇滚。
Well I heard the news there's good rockin' tonight.
过来,快。嘘,安静。来吧。
Come here, quick. Shh, quiet. Come on.
穿过。
Right through there.
约翰尼，你所有的乐器都准备好了。
Johnny, all your instruments are set up on stage.
啊,谢谢。
Ah, thank you.
我要你带上我的摇滚鞋。
I want you to bring along my rockin' shoes.
因为今晚我要用摇滚赶走所有的忧郁，我听说今晚有很棒的摇滚。
'Cause tonight I'm gonna rock away all the blues, I heard the news there's good rockin' tonight.
太棒了，曼德拉草。只是美好的。
That was wonderful, mandrake. Just wonderful.
我们的下一位表演者开始了他的踢踏舞课……回来。你通过。走开，走开。
Our next performer began his tap dancing lessons... Get back. You're through. Go away, go away.
我很抱歉。你的常规程序刚刚被打断了。
I'm sorry. Your regularly scheduled program has just been interrupted.
他在这里做什么?
What's he doing here?
——嘘。-打扰一下。
- Shh. - Excuse me, please.
你们都给我坐下!现在!
You sit down, all of you! Right now!
-对不起，我得走了。-别动，伙计。你表现自己!
- Excuse me, I must go. - Stay put, buddy. You behave yourselves!
很多人都称他为国王。
A lot of people call this guy the king.
女士们先生们，有请猫王!
Ladies and gentlemen, Elvis Presley!
一，二，三，四!
One, two, three, four!
好吧，自从我的孩子离开我，我找到了一个新的住处。
Well, since my baby left me I found a new place to dwell.
在偏僻街道的尽头。
Down on the end of lonely street.
在心碎的酒店嗯，我我感到如此孤独，宝贝我感到如此孤独，我孤独得想死。
At heartbreak hotel well, I I feel so lonely, baby I feel so lonely I get so lonely I could die.
虽然那里总是很拥挤，但你仍然可以为失恋的恋人找到一些空间。
And though it's always crowded you still can find some room for brokenhearted lovers.
在黑暗中哭泣哦，宝贝，我感到如此孤独，宝贝，我感到如此孤独，是的，我感到如此孤独，我想要死去。
To cry there in the gloom oh, baby I feel so lonely, baby I feel so lonely, yeah I feel so lonely I could die.
服务员的眼泪一直在流前台服务员穿着黑色衣服。
Well the bellhop's tears keep flowing the desk clerk's dressed in black.
他们在孤独的街道上走了那么久，他们永远不会回去哦，宝贝，我好孤独，宝贝，我好孤独，我好孤独，我想死。
They been so long on lonely street they ain't never going back oh, baby I get so lonely, baby I get so lonely I get so lonely I could die.
可怜。
Have mercy.
走,约翰尼!
Go, Johnny!
所以如果你的宝宝离开了你。
So if your baby leaves you.
你有故事可讲。
And you've got a tale to tell.
走在寂寞的街道上，去心碎的酒店。
Just take a walk down lonely street to heartbreak hotel.
我好孤独，宝贝，我好孤独，宝贝，我好孤独，我要死了。
I get so lonely, baby I get so lonely, baby, I get so lonely I could die.
Well I get so lonely, baby I feel so lonely, baby I get so lonely I could die.
非常感谢，女士们先生们。
Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen.
约翰尼·沃尔夫和狼群。
Johnny wolfe and the wolfepack.
他们会教你们怎么摇滚。
They'll teach you people how to rock 'n' roll.
每个人都出来…除了这个小家伙。
Everybody out... All except this little one right here.
_“嘿，乔治。
_ “ell - hey, George.
-你去哪了，伙计?-说来话长。
- Where you been, man? - That's a long story.
-听着，孩子们都在里面。——好的。
- Listen, the boys are all inside. - All right.
你觉得我的发型怎么样?——爱。
- How do you like my hair? - Love it.
你们在想什么，孩子们?
Well, what are you thinkin', boys?
-嘿，你剪头发了吗?-你去哪了，伙计?我们错过了你。
- Hey, did you get a haircut? - Where you been, man? We missed you.
给我几分钟。
Give me a few minutes.
玛丽……我想让你知道，如果有任何办法…-我可以…——我知道。
Marie... I want you to know that if there was any way... - I could... - I know.
当我和你在一起的时候，我发现了一些我以为早已消失的东西。
When I was with you, I found somethin' I thought was long gone.
我想留着它。
I want to hold on to it.
我觉得如果我回到飞机上…它会再次从我身边溜走。
I feel like if I get back on that plane... It's gonna slip away from me again.
我会一直为你留一间空房间的。
I'll always keep a room vacant for you.
我会想你的。
I'm gonna miss you.
我也会想你的…“因为我从来不知道有个爸爸是什么感觉。”
I'm gonna miss you too... "Cause I never knew what it was like to have a dad."
现在我做的。
Now I do.
“E。“来吧，伙计。我们得走了。
“E.” come on, man. We've gotta go.
我马上就来。
I'll be right there.
我第一次见到你的时候，我一点都不喜欢你。
When I first met you, I didn't like you at all.
我以为你是最刻薄的…我见过最傲慢自私的小混蛋。
I thought you were the meanest... Most arrogant, selfish little bastard I'd ever met.
然后想到你让我想起了我像你这么大的时候。
Then got to thinkin' how much you reminded me of me when I was your age.
我都忘了当个坏蛋，做个反叛者的感觉有多好了。
I forgot how good it felt to be a bad-ass, to be a rebel.
你让我觉得自己又像猫王了。
You made me feel like Elvis again.
嘿,猫王。
Hey, Elvis.
谢谢你今晚。我知道你是为了我。
Thanks for tonight. I know you did that for me.
地狱,不,孩子。我这样做是为了摇滚。
Hell, no, kid. I did it for rock 'n' roll.
嘿,猫王!
Hey, Elvis!
你还是国王。
You're still the king.
一定有更亮的灯。
There must be lights burning brighter.
在某处。
Somewhere.
如果我能梦到一个更好的地方，在那里我所有的兄弟手牵手，我就能像鸟儿一样在更蓝的天空中飞得更高。
Got to be birds flying higher in a sky more blue if I can dream of a better land where all my brothers walk hand-in-hand.
告诉我为什么，为什么，为什么，为什么我的梦想不能实现。
Tell me why oh, why, oh, why can't my dream come true.
哦,为什么。
Oh, why.
总会有和平与理解的时候。
There must be peace and understanding sometime.
承诺的强风，会吹走怀疑和恐惧。
Strong winds of promise, that will blow away the doubt and fear.
如果能梦见一个更温暖的太阳。
If can dream of a warmer sun.
在那里，希望一直照耀着每个人。
Where hope keeps shining on everyone.
告诉我为什么，为什么，为什么太阳不再出现……
Tell me why oh, why, oh, why won't that sun appear...
我们迷失在云中。
We're lost in a cloud.
雨水太多了。
With too much rain.
我们被困在一个充满痛苦的世界里。
We're trapped in a world that's troubled with pain.
但只要一个人。
But as long as a man.
拥有梦想的力量…他可以救赎自己的灵魂，然后飞翔。
Has the strength to dream... He can redeem his soul and fly.
在我的内心深处。
Deep in my heart.
还有一个令人颤抖的问题，我确信答案，答案总会出现的。
There's a trembling question still I am sure that the answer's the answer's gonna come somehow.
在黑暗中。
Out there in the dark.
这是一个召唤蜡烛，是的。
There's a beckoning candle yeah.
只要我能思考，只要我能说话，只要我能站，只要我能走，只要我能做梦，我就能感受到我的梦想。
And while I can think while I can talk while I can stand while I can walk while I can dream I'm feelin' my dream.
成真。
Come true.
哇。
Whoa.
现在。
Right now.
让它现在成真，哦耶。
Let it come true right now oh yeah.
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
打破它，燃烧它。
Break it, burn it.
到处拖着它，拧着它，转动它，你不能把它推倒，因为每一分钟每一小时。
Drag it all around, twist it, turn it, you can't tear it down 'cause every minute every hour.
你会被这种奇怪而强大的力量所震撼……我的爱。
You'll be shaken by the strange and mighty power... Of my love.
粉碎它，踢它。
Crush it, kick it.
你永远赢不了。
You can never win.
不，宝贝，你不能舔它。
No, baby, you can't lick it.
我会让你走到最后。
I'll make you the end.
每一分钟每一小时。
And every minute every hour.
你会被这种奇怪而强大的力量所震撼……我的爱。
You'll be shaken by the strange and mighty power... Of my love.
我说过每分钟每小时。
I said that every minute every hour.
你会被这种奇怪而强大的力量所震撼……我的爱。
You'll be shaken by the strange and mighty power... Of my love.
我说过每分钟每小时。
I said that every minute every hour.
你会被这种奇怪而强大的力量所震撼……我的爱,
You'll be shaken by the strange and mighty power... Of my love,
是的，每分钟每小时。
yeah, every minute every hour.
你会被奇怪的事物震撼……
You'll be shaken by the strange...